<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ICASSP 2022</title>
    <link>./</link>
    <description>Recent content on ICASSP 2022</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 09:26:16 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Program Chairs’ Welcome</title>
      <link>./tp_overview.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 09:08:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>./tp_overview.html</guid>
      <description>Woon-Seng Gan
Professor,
Nanyang Technological University   Kai-Kuang Ma
Professor,
Nanyang Technological University    It is our greatest pleasure to welcome all of you to the first tandem-hybrid ICASSP 2022. ICASSP is the world’s largest and most comprehensive technical conference focused on signal processing and its applications. This year’s edition of ICASSP is a departure from the virtual conferences held over the past two years due to the COVID-19 pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizing Committee</title>
      <link>./organizing_committee.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 09:11:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>./organizing_committee.html</guid>
      <description>General ChairHaizhou Li, CUHK (Shenzhen), China; NUS, Singapore  General Co-ChairSadaoki Furui, NII, Japan  Honorary ChairTsuhan Chen, NUS, Singapore  Technical Program ChairsWoon-Seng Gan, NTU, Singapore Kai Kuang Ma, NTU, Singapore  Finance ChairLei Wang, COLIPS, Singapore Yan Wu, I2R, A*STAR, Singapore  Operations ChairMinghui Dong, I2R, A*STAR, Singapore  Industry Programs &amp; Exhibition ChairFa-Long Luo , Micron, USA  Plenary ChairJay Kuo, USC, USA Helen Meng, CUHK, HK SAR, China Douglas O&#39;Shaughnessy, INRS, Canada  Special Session ChairJonathon Chambers, Uleicester, UK Zhenggou Li, I2R, A*STAR, Singapore Pina Marzilano, EPFL, Switzerland  Tutorial ChairMauro Barni, USiena, Italy Saeid Sanei, NottinghamTU, UK Tanja Schultz, U Bremen, Germany  Education Program ChairNgai-Man (Man) Cheung, SUTD, Singapore Kenan Emir Ak, I2R, A*STAR, Singapore Rongshan Yu, XMU, China Eng Siong Chng, NTU, Singapore  Grand Challenge ChairAndy Khong, NTU, Singapore Wee Peng Tay, NTU, Singapore  Show and Tell ChairNancy Chen, I2R, A*STAR, Singapore Tomi Kinnunen, UEF, Finland  Sponsorship ChairsZhizheng Wu, Facebook, USA Lei Xie, NWPU, China  Industry Exhibits ChairWei Lu , SUTD, Singapore  Industry Panel ChairSoujanya Poria, SUTD, Singapore  Industry Keynote ChairWei Jiang, German Research Center for Artificial Intelligence (DFKI), Germany  Publication ChairKenneth Lam, HKPU, HK SAR, China Berrak Sisman, SUTD, Singapore Yan Sun, URI, USA  Virtual Conference ChairKong Aik Lee, I2R, A*STAR, Singapore  Workshops ChairSiqi Cai, NUS, Singapore Rong Tong, COLIPS, Singapore  Diversity Program ChairNancy Chen, I2R, A*STAR, Singapore S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Program Committee</title>
      <link>./tpc.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 09:19:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>./tpc.html</guid>
      <description>Technical Program Chairs Woon-Seng Gan
NTU, Singapore
Kai Kuang Ma
NTU, Singapore
Special Session Chairs Jonathon Chambers
Uleicester, UK
Zhenggou Li
I2R, A*STAR, Singapore
Pina Marzilano
EPFL, Switzerland
Applied Signal Processing Systems Ali Akbari
Stanford
Roozbeh Jafari
Texas A&amp;M University
John McAllister
Queen’s University Belfast
Audio and Acoustic Signal Processing Shoko Araki
NTT Communication Science Laboratories
Minje Kim
Indiana University Bloomington
Michael Mandel
Brooklyn College, City University of New York</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviewers</title>
      <link>./reviewers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 09:26:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>./reviewers.html</guid>
      <description>Prathosh A P, IISc
Wallace A. Martins, University of Luxembourg &amp; Federal University of Rio de Janeiro
Ashkan Aazami, Microsoft
Solomon Teferra Abate, Addis Ababa University
Mourad Abbas, High Council of Arabic Language
Albaraesi Abdelhamid, University College London
Ossama Abdel-Hamid, Apple Inc
Maryam Abdolali, University of Mons
Karim Abed-Meraim, University of Orléans
Thushara D. Abhayapala, Australian National University (ANU)
Elias Aboutanios, UNSW Sydney
Vinayak Abrol, University of Oxford
Shady Abu-Hussein, Tel Aviv University</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>